Guide to the Pittsburgh Cultural Trust Records, 1975-2021 CTC.2000.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District Development, 1979-2000; II.
  - District Development files, 1979-2000; 1.
    - Wolf Report, 1989 (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Wood Street 601-607 Azen building, 1989-1992 (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Wood Street station project, 1993-1998 (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - Zoning approvals, 1993 (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - District Development architectural materials, 1984-1996; 2.
    Most of these plans and drawings are centered around the design and construction of the O'Reilly Theatre, Allegheny Riverfront park, and the Theatre Square office building. The plans are arranged in alphabetical order by subject.
    - Allegheny riverfront park - 5 items, April 1995 (Map-case 3, Drawer 2)
    - Art Cinema Renovation - 19 items, 1995 (Map-case 3, Drawer 2)
    - Cinemas at Theater Square Parking Garage - 1 item, March 1994 (Map-case 3, Drawer 2)
    - Cultural District - 5 items (Map-case 3, Drawer 2)
    - Fourth Theater - 6 items, July 29 1996 (Map-case 3, Drawer 3, Drawer 2)
    - Fulton Theater lobby sketches - 3 items, 1994 (Map-case 3, Drawer 3)
    - Liberty Avenue - 6 items (Map-case 3, Drawer 4)
    - Moose Hall - 13 items, 1989 (Map-case 3, Drawer 4)
    - Penn and Liberty historic district - 2 items (Map-case 3, Drawer 4)
    - Pittsburgh Public Theater and the Tower at Theater Square - 3 items, 1993 (Map-case 3, Drawer 4)
    - Pittsburgh Riverfront Park - 15 items, 1995 (Map-case 3, Drawer 4)
    - Plan of property situate in the second ward city of Pittsburgh - 1 item, January 9 1986 (Map-case 3, Drawer 4)
    - Plan of property Stanley Theatre and vicinity - 3 items, January 1984 (Map-case 3, Drawer 4)
    - Theatre Square - 12 items, 1992-1996 (Map-case 3, Drawer 4)
    - Tower at Theater Square - 2 items (Map-case 3, Drawer 4)
- Art Services, 1989-1997; III.
  The art services branch of the Cultural Trust aimed to advise and support other arts organization in the Pittsburgh area. Most of this material centers around workshops that the Trust organized. The subseries is arranged in alphabetical order by folder title.
  - Arts Management Library, 1996 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Arts services, December 1995 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Arts services, 1997 (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Arts services underwriting, 1997-1998 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Evaluation of the Arts Services Programs of the Pittsburgh Cultural Trust by the North Group, July 1991 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Fellowship and Grants for Individual Artists by the Manchester Craftsmen's Guild and the Pittsburgh Center for the Arts, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Hot Topics & Everyday Concerns - a seminar for arts managers on employment regulations tax compliance new FASB guidelines and audits, November 1995 (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - Individual artist list, August 1995 (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts Grant - writing workshop attendance roster, June 1990 (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - Pittsburgh Arts Organizations Finances Public and Private Funding and Impact on the Local Economy by the Pennsylvania Economy League, March 1989 (Box 137, Folder 10)
  - Pittsburgh Arts Resources Cultural Directories (Box 137, Folder 11)
  - Pittsburgh Arts Resources Cultural Directories (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - ProArts, 1997 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Starting a Nonprofit Organization - where to begin, 1996 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - TIX for Teachers, 1994-1995 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Workshops miscellaneous notes, 1995-1997 (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Workshops 89 marketing roundtable, March 1989 (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - Workshops 91-92, 1990-1991 (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - Workshops 91-92 design, 1991 (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - Workshops 91-92 design marketing roundtable, 1991 (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - Workshops 91-92 new board members, 1991 (Box 138, Folder 10)
  - Workshops 91-92 PCA grants, 1991 (Box 138, Folder 11)
  - Workshops 91-92 prognostication and performance, 1991 (Box 138, Folder 12)
  - Workshops 92-93 fundraising, 1992 (Box 138, Folder 13)
  - Workshops 92-93 multicultural, 1992 (Box 138, Folder 14)
  - Workshops 92-93 PCA grants, 1992 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Workshops 92-93 PCA grants individual, 1992 (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Workshops 93-94 PCA grants, 1992-1993 (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Workshops 94-95 budget, 1994 (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Workshops 94-95 Micki Hobson, 1994 (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Workshops 94-95 planning, 1994 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Workshops 94-95 publication, 1994-1995 (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - Workshops 95-96, 1995-1996 (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Workshops 95-96 attendance cards, 1995-1996 (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - Workshops 95-96 computer use in arts organizations, 1995-1996 (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - Workshops 95-96 cyberbasics, 1996 (Box 139, Folder 11)
  - Workshops 95-96 development, 1995 (Box 139, Folder 12)
  - Workshops 95-96 fall, 1996 (Box 139, Folder 13)
  - Workshops 95-96 notes, 1996 (Box 139, Folder 14)
  - Workshops 95-96 outreach, 1995-1996 (Box 139, Folder 15)
  - Workshops 95-96 series subscription, 1995-1996 (Box 139, Folder 16)
  - Workshops 96-97 fund raising for arts organizations, 1994-1997 (Box 139, Folder 17)
- Harris Theatre / Art Cinema Renovation, 1989-1995; IV.
  Arranged in this series is the materials that relate to the renovation of the Art Cinema at 809 Liberty Avenue. The venue was renamed the Harris Theatre after the project was completed in November 1995.
  - Air Conditioning seating marquees and risors, 1995 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Air Monitoring Results for Arts Cinema Building by Allegheny Asbestos Analysis Inc., January 1995 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Asbestos and Lead Based Paint Abatement for Arts Cinema Building by Allegheny Asbestos Analysis Inc., December 1994 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Bohlin Cywinski Jackson architects, 1994 (Box 140, Folder 4-5)
  - Budget projections and cost estimates, 1994 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Comparison Estimates for Arts Cinema Renovation by Jendoco Construction Corporation, November 1994 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Concessions equipment, 1994-1995 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Environmental issues, 1994-1995 (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Jendoco construction budgets, 1989-1996 (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - Opening, 1995 (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - Pittsburgh Filmmakers, 1991-1994 (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - Redevelopment, 1989-1994 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Renovations to the Arts Cinema at 809 Liberty Avenue by Bohlin Cywinski Jackson architects, November 1994 (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Sound and lighting, 1994-1995 (Box 142, Folder 3)
- Institutional Development, 1986-1998; V.
  The fifth series in the collection groups together the files regarding the financial campaigns of the Cultural Trust. The series is split into two subseries. One, contains the records of the yearly campaign and the other all other institutional development office files.
  - Annual Campaign files, 1990-1998; 1.
    These files are arranged chronologically by campaign season and then alphabetically by folder title. The majority of these files contain copies of the letters to individual and corporate donors.
    - Annual Campaign 90-91 fall mailing, 1990 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Annual Campaign 90-91 fall solicitation letters, September 1990 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Annual Campaign 90-91 winter solicitation letters, December 1990 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Annual Campaign 90-91 summary report, March 1992 (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Annual Campaign 90-91 spring mailing, March 1991 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Annual Campaign 91-92 fall mailing, 1991-1992 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Annual Campaign 91-92 fall letters, 1991-1992 (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - Annual Campaign 91-92 benefits, 1991 (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Annual Campaign 91-92 corporate campaign, 1991-1992 (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - Annual Campaign 91-92 correspondence, 1992 (Box 143, Folder 10)
    - Annual Campaign 91-92 lapsed donors, 1992 (Box 143, Folder 11)
    - Annual Campaign 91-92 summary report, May 1992 (Box 143, Folder 12)
    - Annual Campaign 91-92 spring mailing (Box 143, Folder 13)
    - Annual Campaign 92-93, 1992 (Box 143, Folder 14)
    - Annual Campaign 92-93 corporate follow up, March 1993 (Box 143, Folder 15)
    - Annual Campaign 92-93 corporate mailing temporary do not mail, March 1993 (Box 143, Folder 16)
    - Annual Campaign 92-93 corporate reply card, November 1992 (Box 143, Folder 17)
    - Annual Campaign 92-93 fall mailing, September 1992 (Box 143, Folder 18)
    - Annual Campaign 92-93 premiums, 1991-1992 (Box 143, Folder 19)
    - Annual Campaign 92-93 procedures, 1990-1993 (Box 143, Folder 20)
    - Annual Campaign 92-93 spring mailing, 1992-1993 (Box 143, Folder 21)
    - Annual Campaign 92-93 staff campaign, 1992 (Box 143, Folder 22)
    - Annual Campaign 92-93 stationary, 1992 (Box 143, Folder 23)
    - Annual Campaign 92-93 summary, September 1992 (Box 143, Folder 24)
    - Annual Campaign 92-93 winter mailing, September 1992 (Box 143, Folder 25)
    - Annual Campaign 93-94 Blast-Off memberships, 1994 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Annual Campaign 93-94 cast party invitations, 1993-1994 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Annual Campaign 93-94 correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Annual Campaign 93-94 corporate campaign, 1993-1994 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Annual Campaign 93-94 corporate temporary "do not mails", 1993-1994 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Annual Campaign 93-94 corporate follow-up mailing, 1994 (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Annual Campaign 93-94 donor feedback, 1993 (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Annual Campaign 93-94 fall mailing, 1993-1994 (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - Annual Campaign 93-94 fall lists, 1993 (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - Annual Campaign 93-94 individual mailing, 1993-1994 (Box 144, Folder 10)
    - Annual Campaign 93-94 lapsed foundation mailing, 1994 (Box 144, Folder 11)
    - Annual Campaign 93-94 premiums, 1993-1994 (Box 144, Folder 12)
    - Annual Campaign 93-94 spring mailing, 1994 (Box 144, Folder 13)
    - Annual Campaign 93-94 staff campaign, 1993-1994 (Box 144, Folder 14)
    - Annual Campaign 93-94 summary reports, November 1993 (Box 144, Folder 15)
    - Annual Campaign 93-94 winter corporate mailing, 1993 (Box 144, Folder 16)
    - Annual Campaign 93-94 winter mailing, 1993 (Box 144, Folder 17)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 business subcommittee correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 business subcommittee meeting minutes, 1994-1995 (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 business subcommittee miscellaneous, May 1995 (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 business subcommittee reports, 1994-1995 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 cast party invitations, 1995-1996 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 corporate mailing fall, 1994 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 corporate mailing spring, 1995 (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 development committee correspondence, 1990-1995 (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 development committee meeting minutes, 1994-1995 (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 development committee miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 145, Folder 11)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 development committee reports, 1994-1995 (Box 145, Folder 12)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 district property owners, 1994-1995 (Box 145, Folder 13)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 individual fall mailing, 1994 (Box 145, Folder 14)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 individual lapsed donors, June 1994 (Box 145, Folder 15)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 individual spring mailing, November 1994 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 individual subcommittee correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 individual subcommittee meeting minutes, 1994-1995 (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 individual subcommittee miscellaneous, 1994-1995 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 individual winter mailing, 1994-1995 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 lapsed donors spring, April 1995 (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 lapsed donors winter, December 1994 (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 Live on Stage offer, 1994-1995 (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 premiums, 1994 (Box 146, Folder 9)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 special events subcommittee, 1994-1995 (Box 146, Folder 10)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 staff campaign, 1994 (Box 146, Folder 11)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 stationary, 1994 (Box 146, Folder 12)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 thank you letters, 1994-1995 (Box 146, Folder 13)
    - Annual Campaign 94-95 TIX for Teachers mailing, 1995 (Box 146, Folder 14)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 board solicitation, 1995-1996 (Box 146, Folder 15)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 business donor reception, September 1996 (Box 146, Folder 16)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 business fall mailing, October 1995 (Box 146, Folder 17)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 business follow-up mailing, October 1995 (Box 146, Folder 18)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 business spring mailing, 1996 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 business subcommittee correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 business subcommittee meeting minutes, 1995-1996 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 Cats premium business fall and winter mailing, 1995-1996 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 corporate fall mailing, 1995-1996 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 development committee correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 development committee meeting minutes, 1995-1996 (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 development committee reception, August 1996 (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 development committee solicitation, 1995 (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 foundation proposals, 1995-1996 (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 individual fall mailing, 1995 (Box 147, Folder 11)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 individual spring mailing, 1996 (Box 147, Folder 12)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 individual spring mailing usher personalization, April 1996 (Box 147, Folder 13)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 individual subcommittee correspondence, 1995 (Box 147, Folder 14)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 individual subcommittee volunteer recruitment, 1996 (Box 147, Folder 15)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 individual winter mailing, 1995 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 individual winter mailing miscellaneous solicitations, November 1995 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 individual winter mailing usher personalization, 1995 (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 les Miserables premium, 1996 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 Live on Stage membership offer, 1995-1996 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 miscellaneous business requests, 1995-1996 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 miscellaneous individual requests, 1995-1996 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 premiums, 1995-1996 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 staff campaign, 1995 (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Annual Campaign 95-96 stationary, 1995 (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 business fall mailing, September 1996 (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 board personalization individual winter mailing, 1996 (Box 148, Folder 12)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 board solicitation, 1996-1997 (Box 148, Folder 13)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 business follow-up, January 1997 (Box 148, Folder 14)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 business follow-up, July 1997 (Box 148, Folder 15)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 business spring mailing, April 1997 (Box 148, Folder 16)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 business subcommittee correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 business subcommittee meeting minutes, July 1997 (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 business winter mailing, December 1996 (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 cast parties, 1996 (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 a Chorus Line premium, 1996-1997 (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 development committee correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 development committee meeting minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 development committee solicitation, 1996 (Box 149, Folder 9)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 donor listing (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 donor lounge premium, 1996-1997 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 foundation proposals, 1996-1997 (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 Grease premium, 1996 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 individual campaign summer follow-up, August 1997 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 individual fall mailing, 1996 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 individual spring mailing, 1997 (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 individual subcommittee correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 individual subcommittee meeting minutes, July 1996 (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 individual winter mailing, 1996 (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 Live on Stage offer, 1996-1997 (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 miscellaneous business spring requests, 1997 (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 miscellaneous business winter requests, 1996- 1997 (Box 150, Folder 13)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 miscellaneous individual spring appeals, June 1997 (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 miscellaneous individual winter requests, 1996- 1997 (Box 150, Folder 15)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 planning, 1996- 1997 (Box 150, Folder 16)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 premiums, 1997 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 renewal rates, July 1997 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 stationary materials, 1996 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 summary reports, 1996-1998 (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 staff campaign, 1996 (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 volunteer recruitment, 1996 (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 usher personalization fall, October 1996 (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 usher personalization spring, April 1997 (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Annual Campaign 96-97 usher personalization winter, December 1996 (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Annual Campaign 97-98 Broadway lounge, 1997-1998 (Box 151, Folder 10)
    - Annual Campaign 97-98 business committee correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 151, Folder 11)
    - Annual Campaign 97-98 business committee meetings, 1997-1998 (Box 151, Folder 12)
    - Annual Campaign 97-98 business campaign reports, 1998 (Box 151, Folder 13)
    - Annual Campaign 97-98 cast parties, 1997-1998 (Box 151, Folder 14)
    - Annual Campaign 97-98 correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 151, Folder 15)
    - Annual Campaign 97-98 development committee correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 151, Folder 16)
    - Annual Campaign 97-98 development committee meeting minutes, 1998 (Box 151, Folder 17)
    - Annual Campaign 97-98 events, 1997 (Box 151, Folder 18)
    - Annual Campaign 97-98 business fall solicitations, 1997-1998 (Box 151, Folder 19)
    - Annual Campaign 97-98 spring business solicitations, April 1998 (Box 151, Folder 20)
    - Annual Campaign 97-98 foundation proposals, 1997-1998 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Annual Campaign 97-98 individual committee correspondence, October 1997 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Annual Campaign 97-98 individual committee meeting minutes (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Annual Campaign 97-98 individual fall solicitations, 1997 (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Annual Campaign 97-98 individual spring solicitations, 1998 (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Annual Campaign 97-98 Live on Stage business premium, 1998 (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Annual Campaign 97-98 materials and stationery, 1997-1998 (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Annual Campaign 97-98 membership research and evaluation, 1996-1997 (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Annual Campaign 97-98 miscellaneous mailings, 1997-1998 (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - Annual Campaign 97-98 planning, 1997 (Box 152, Folder 10)
    - Annual Campaign 97-98 premiums, 1997 (Box 152, Folder 11)
    - Annual Campaign 97-98 staff campaign, 1997 (Box 152, Folder 12)
    - Annual Campaign account notes and articles, 1995-1997 (Box 152, Folder 13)
    - Annual Campaign cumulative direct mail statistics, 1994 (Box 152, Folder 14)
    - Annual Campaign development committee lists, 1995-1997 (Box 152, Folder 15)
    - Annual Campaign distribution of funds (Box 152, Folder 16)
  - Institutional Development files, 1986-1998; 2.
    This subseries consists of files related to the financial requests by the Cultural Trust to various federal institutions, grant foundations, and development groups. It also contains planning documents for various fundraisers that the Trust organized. The files are arranged alphabetically by folder subject.
    - Allegheny Regional Asset District 1995 close-out report, February 1996 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - Allegheny Regional Asset District 1995 proposal, 1994-1996 (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - Allegheny Regional Asset District 1996, 1993-1995 (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - Allegheny Regional Asset District 1996 capital proposal, 1995-1997 (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - Allegheny Regional Asset District 1996 operating proposal, 1995-1996 (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - Allegheny Regional Asset District 1996 close-out report, 1996-1997 (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - Calendar mailing to donors, December 1990 (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Calendar mailing to donors, March 1991 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Calendar mailing to donors, June 1991 (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Calendar mailing to donors, December 1991 (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Calendar mailing to donors, March 1992 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Calendar mailing to donors, September 1992 (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - Calendar mailing to donors, November 1992 (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - Calendar mailing to donors, February 1993 (Box 154, Folder 8)
    - Calendar mailing to donors, May 1993 (Box 154, Folder 9)
    - Calendar mailing to donors, August 1993 (Box 154, Folder 10)
    - Calendar mailing to donors, November 1993 (Box 154, Folder 11)
    - Calendar mailing to donors, February 1994 - August 1995 (Box 154, Folder 12)
    - Calendar mailing to donors, February 1997 (Box 154, Folder 13)
    - Calendar mailing to donors, May 1997 (Box 154, Folder 14)
    - Calendar mailing to donors, August 1997 (Box 154, Folder 15)
    - Calendar mailing to donors, November 1997 (Box 154, Folder 16)
    - Calendar mailing to donors, February 1998 (Box 154, Folder 17)
    - Calendar mailing to donors, May 1998 (Box 154, Folder 18)
    - Capital campaign engraving of plaques, 1988-1989 (Box 154, Folder 19)
    - Capital campaign seat plaques, 1988-1989 (Box 154, Folder 20)
    - City of Pittsburgh community development block grant proposal (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - City of Pittsburgh community development block grant invoice form (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - City of Pittsburgh community development 1992 block grant, 1992-1994 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - City of Pittsburgh community development 1993 block grant, 1993-1995 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Executive management binder, 1991 (Box 156, Folder 1-3)
    - Fulton theater opening, 1991 (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Fulton theater opening mailing list, 1989-1991 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Fulton theater opening party, May 1991 (Box 156, Folder 6-7)
    - Howard Heinz endowment FY 1987 request number 1 October 1986 funded December 1986, 1986-1987 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Howard Heinz endowment FY 1987 request number 2 April 1987 (Box 157, Folder 2)